Spoonful of Sugar is a horror film directed by Mercedes Bryce Morgan.
Millicent, working on her thesis about children with severe allergies, is hired to babysit
little Johnny, a sickly, mute child who suffers from every allergy under the sun.
As she discovers Johnny’s dark family secrets, things begin to become unhinged.
Millicent, played by Morgan Saylor.
Rebecca, played by Kat Foster.
Jacob, played by Myko Olivier.
Johnny, played by Danilo Crovetti.
Little Girl, played by Christiana Montoya.
Spoonful of Sugar is a 2022 American horror thriller film that was directed by
Mercedes Bryce Morgan, based on a script written by Leah Saint Marie.
It stars Morgan Saylor, Kat Foster, Danilo
Crovetti, Myko Olivier and Keith Powell.
The film centers on a college student who takes on a job caring for a sickly child, only for
things to go horribly wrong when she offers him some of her own medication.
The tone is dark.